One of you will be taken hostage.
Hostage?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
The next hostage is Mr. Risen.
We have to protect him. This is, seriously.
The game we have to play in order to rescue him is...
Don't drop the tissues!
Don't drop the tissue.
For the number of seconds you are given, you are to look up in a circle and try not to drop the tissue.
Starting with the first person, 3 seconds, 5 seconds, 7 seconds, 10 seconds
Oooh.
But doesn't that sound easy?
Sure, it's a tissue.
It looks like it'll float.
I think it's gonna float. I think it's gonna float.
What do you think, Mr. Rissei?
I wonder if it's true.
Trust me.
I used to use it every day.
I thought I could do it.
We don't do this kind of thing.
I'm a little nervous.
I'll be fine.
Okay, first one's three seconds.
Who's going to do it?
I'm not very strong.
I think I can make it this far.
I need to be flexible.
I think we should go first on this one.
Three seconds.
I think I can do three seconds.
I want to do it in three seconds.
I'll count from the moment you take your hand away.
Isn't it really high?
Is it too high?
Can you do it for me, please?
Please.
I only have one shot.
I only got one shot.
You think he'll be okay?
I'll think of a plan.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to do it if I flap my wings too much.
Patapapap!
There we go.
Hmm...
Now, please give me the tissue you drop, Mr. Otsuchi.
Yes, please.
Here we go.
Three, two, one.
Yay!
It was good.
It was so good.
It's amazing. It's amazing.
You should go lighter.
You should go hard.
And now the second person, who would like to take the challenge?
I do.
Okay, I'll do it.
I'm sorry, if Panchatu...
I'm not sure yet.
Then, Mr. Wada, please.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four, five.
That's OK.
Yeah!
I got it!
That's good!
That was good!
I hope I can make it work the way Chish wants it to.
Yeah, I'm sure you're right.
Get the police cars out, Sweets.
There's a lot of Healeys in there.
I'll get it right.
Yes, sir. Well done, sir.
That's great!
Thank you!
And who will be the third?
Yes, I'll go.
Ms. Miyagi.
Ms. Migi, you are the type of person who can do pretty much anything.
Now, Mr. Imamura.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, I'll do it.
Wow!
Two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Success! It worked.
That's great!
This is the hard part.
You're a man of reason, aren't you?
Whoever did this...
So, the last one is Shinasa, right?
Yes, sir!Yes!
I'm seriously scared.
I'm really scared.
I just did 7 seconds with Mr. Imamura.
How about 10 seconds?
Ten seconds.
What?
But I've got no choice.
Now that everyone's connected.
I can't wait to get you out of here.
I'd like to rescue them from this place.
I'll do my best.
Last four in 10 seconds.
Mr. Shijan.
I'm counting on you.
Next preview.
Please do.
Here we go.
Let's go!
One, two, three.
Ahhh!
This, this, this.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I thought it looked pretty good.
We were told together.
I thought I could do it so much better.
One, two, three.
Sorry!
Go!
One, two, three.
Aaaaah!
Oh, no!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
That's what's wrong with me!
Why do you love your friends?
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry!
If you want, I'll let you be the victim!
Please!
Woooo!
Woooooo!
Oh no, this is scary.
Scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary, scary!
Mizui-chan has gone crazy.
I'm really, really, really taking the liberty of giving it to you.
I'm really, really, really going to take the liberty of giving it to you.
I'm so sorry.
No, thank you.
How do you feel now?
I was so close.
I thought I could make it.
You're too kind!
I'm a senior!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Next, we have Ms. Utsumi.
Why? Why?
Help me!
I want to do it!
I want to do it! I want to do it!
I feel like a scout.
I'm feeling a scout, and I'm feeling the souls of the people
I'm feeling the belly, the souls of the people who made the first team.
I kinda get it.
The challenge for you to rescue them is...
Paper airplanes.
Oh, wow!
I bet you all had one of those when you were little.
I used to use them when I was a little girl.
Now I'm going to give you all
I'm going to give you origami paper.
You can make your own paper airplanes.
I see!
The first person will fly first.
The next one...
The next one will fly farther than the first one.
Farther than the distance the first one flew.
I think I can do it.
I'm sure of it.
Next announcement
Let's fly for me
Let's make it fly
Looking at it so far...
23 or 34 something seems like it's going to fly pretty well.
Pokey?
Yeah.
The voices are getting louder and louder.
Are you okay, Momochan?
Poi!
What about Momochan?
Momochan!
Momochan, are you sure it's folded?
The print on the bag...
I feel like it stinks.
They're chasing us because they feel like it.
That's right, I'm chasing after it.
That's right, I'm chasing after it.Yes, I'm feeling a little stuck.
Okay, I'll go see Dr. Monkey first.
I'll be right back.
Just break it here, okay? Here.
Oh, yeah. I'm really counting on you.
Please, doctor.
Please, please, please.
Here we go.
[fast forward]
Aaaaahhhhhh! It's clear, sir.
And the second one, skip to the next one... and the second one, skip to the next one... and the second one, skip to the next one... and the second one, skip to the next one.
You're wrong.
I have a feeling that's the case, Risten, just for about 5 minutes.
Just a little bit.
I'll take care of it.
Ani...
simultan
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What a pity.
Let's see, one more chance.
If only one person succeeds, two people succeed.
Two chances for one person.
Two chances for each of us.
Well, that's okay. Let's make it two chances per person.
Thank you very much.
I'll just skip it.
On the contrary, I'm going to give it to Hinase-chan,
I'll skip it.
So, two times for crying out loud, two times challenge, right?
Let's do it like this. Let's do it this way.
I'm begging you.
A style of bumping into and changing things.
Ahhh...
Sorry.
Well then...
I'm sorry
Mr. Utsuyu, I'm going to ask you to become a victim here.
Please.
Ahhh...
I can't do it anymore.
You're so happy.
This is like the third time's the charm.
Third time's the charm.
The last hostage is Mr. Takao.
I'm really bad with balloons.
But I believe in you, my friends.
Go above and beyond.
Go above and beyond! Go above and beyond!
Team Esteem48... at least at the end.
Yes, because if it's over, it's over.
The game we're going to challenge you to is...
"Guru Butt.
Oh!
I'm really good at batting.
That's great.
You have to go around a certain number of times.
You have five seconds to press the button
Press the button.
Okay.
Okay, first three times around, then the goal.
Okay, I'll go to the bat.
Go for it.
You really have to mean it.
How can I not?
Yae, this is your third time with the bat.
Please.
Please count.
One.
Oh no!
Two.
Three.
A-ha-ha-ha
Oh no!
This is bad.
Yes, it's a success.
Three is bad.
Then five.
And here we go.
Saramo, you're so stable, aren't you?
I feel good.
Yeah, I feel good.
Okay, second one.
Five times.
Five, yes.
Shinano-san, please.
Please.
Five, two, one.
Oh, something's wrong with the speed.
Three, four. Oh, not at all.
Five, start.
Oh! But that was a close one.
We made it.
Aah! I knew it.
Wow!
That's pretty amazing! Isn't it amazing?
I haven't done this in a while.
No, thank you.
But it was good! It was pretty badass.But it was good! It was pretty bad.
The turning...
I can go around in the same position I was going around.
You can do it as many times as you want.
But after I threw it away, the world was already moving.
Three times is not enough.
You can't see any more.
I don't know where I am.
Then seven.
Who's up for a challenge?
Oh!
I'm sure you can do it, too.
I'm okay.
I was on a boat.
I see.
Maybe I'm strong.
Strong.
Mr. Imamura, please.
I'm counting on you.
I'll go.
Good luck!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
It's a success.
Look out!
Oh, my God.
That's pretty good, isn't it?
How many seconds?
I just did it for about four seconds.
Dangerous.
About four or five.
We're going in circles.
Last one then.
Yes, sir.
I've been spinning around with my friends.
I've been playing with it for a long time, enjoying the distortion.
No, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Yes.
It's like that, isn't it?
I wonder what kind of games we play.
Okay, Mr. Rissen, let's take the bat challenge as a group.
Ten times, please.
Please.
Come on.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Yay!
awesome!
This is so much fun.
Are you okay?
I'm getting used to playing.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
He was scared.
So I tried to spin the balloon.
That's cool.
Thank you for your hard work.
Next episode's preview
I wonder what it will be when the unity comes out
before we know more
that's all I have to say
Thank you very much.
I'm glad
If you found this video interesting
If you found this video interesting, please give it a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
Please watch the next video!